Everyone has something up their sleeve.
The Outfit is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Graham Moore.
Leonard is an English tailor who used to craft suits
on London’s world-famous Savile Row.
After a personal tragedy, he’s ended up in Chicago, operating a small tailor shop in a rough part of town where he
makes beautiful clothes for the only people around who can afford them: a family of vicious gangsters.
Leonard Burling, played by Mark Rylance.
Mable Shaun, played by Zoey Deutch.
Francis, played by Johnny Flynn.
Richie Boyle, played by Dylan O'Brien.
Roy Boyle, played by Simon Russell Beale.
Violet LaFontaine, played by Nikki Amuka-Bird.
The Outfit is a 2022 American psychological thriller crime drama film directed by Graham
Moore in his directorial debut from a screenplay by Moore and Johnathan McClain.
The film stars Mark Rylance, who leads an ensemble cast including Zoey Deutch,
Johnny Flynn, Dylan O'Brien, Nikki Amuka-Bird, and Simon Russell Beale.
Rylance plays an English cutter who runs a tailor shop in Chicago,
whose customers include a group of vicious gangsters.
The film premiered at the 72nd Berlin International Film Festival on February 14, 2022, and was released in
the United States on March 18, 2022, by Focus Features, to positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of chicago, illinois,
gangster, murder, mobster, organized crime.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.